[Music]
Mummy,
yes, take it, our son has come after studying,
our son has studied and become a DM or a
minister, he has brought glory to his parents, I am
hungry, give me food, take the same food and
eat it son, I am cleaning the house.
Laddoo
no no no what about the milkman hey
Ram, I have come, I have given all the milk, I had cooked the milk and
kept it, I thought that today I will make curd and give buttermilk,
this Hamza, keep it all, don't run, run,
see where, eat it all
[Music]
you run, run
hey mummy hey it looks good, it looks good
now you will improve, run, run,
you
[Music]
stand up, it does
n't seem like you have hit me too hard, Nanaka
stand up
hey my mother
Nanaka rest ba
Sushma sister, my son is not getting any relief,
you also keep beating your children for milk,
sister I don't know if our child gets hit so
hard, he will get relief, don't
cry
sister I did not hit him intentionally, it hit me unknowingly, I
hold my ears, from today onwards I will never
hit my child again